A Guide to the James Hugo Johnston, Jr. Papers 1876-1962
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Johnston Papers-Photographs
  - Non Family Photo's
    - R.O.T.C. 1951 (Box-folder 13:32)
    - R.O.T.C. 1953 (A) (Box-folder 13:33)
    - R.O.T.C. 1953 (B) (Box-folder 13:34)
    - R.O.T.C. 1954 (Box-folder 13:35)
    - R.O.T.C. No Date (Box-folder 13:36)
    - R.O.T.C. No Date (Box-folder 13:37)
    - James Hugo Johnston R.O.T.C (Box-folder 13:38)
    - R.O.T.C Summer Camp (Box-folder 13:39)
    - Student Publication Assembly (Box-folder 13:40)
    - Theresita (Box-folder 13:41)
    - V.S.U. Administrators No Date (Box-folder 13:42)
    - The New Virginia Hall (Box-folder 13:43)
    - Women's Week (Box-folder 13:44)
    - Unidentified Children (Box-folder 13:45)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:46)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:47)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:48)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:49)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:50)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 13:51)
    - Unidentified Male (Box-folder 13:52)
    - Photo
      The Photo shows the band at Virginia Union University sitting on the steps of a building. The band consisted of nine members the instruments ranged from the cello, trumpet, trombone snare drum, violin and snare drum.
    - Photo
      This Photo shows seven Virginia Union University male Graduates in thier caps and gowns. Each Graduate has his seperate picture.
    - Photo
      The Photo shows twelve male Graduates of Virginia Union University in a Formal Class Picture.
- Printed
  - Degrees
    - Virginia Normal & Industrial Institute May 15, MDCCCCVIII James Hugo Johnston SR., Public School Teacher Degree (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Virginia Normal & Industrial Institute May 15, 1903 Lowell P. Johnston, Public School Teacher Degree (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Virginia Union University June 4, 1913 James Hugo Johnston Jr., Bachelor of Arts Degree> (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Virginia Union University June 5, 1929 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - University of Chicago July 7, CDDCCCCXXV James Hugo Johnston Jr., Masters of Arts Degree (Box-folder 14:5)
    - University of Chicago March 16,1937 James Hugo Johnston, Docter of Philosophy Degree (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Honors
    - Virginia State College Alumni Association 1959 James Hugo Johnston (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Newspapers
    - The Mirror Vol. 1 No. 2 September 26, 1903 Danville, Va (Box-folder a.)
    - The Mirror Vol. 1 No. 3 October 3, 1903 Danville, Va (Box-folder b.)
    - The Mirror Vol. 1 No. 4 October 10, 1903 Danville, Va (Box-folder c.)
    - The Bee May 23, 1908 Danville, Va (Box-folder d.)